Let's start with a table completion exercise.
Here are the steps for this question type.
In step one, you have to read the
requirements to identify the word limit.
In this exercise, the word limit is no
more than two words.
In step two, you have to read the
title of the table to understand the topic
of the recording.
The title of this table is Places to
Visit in Harbour Heritage, so we are going
to listen to information about some tourist attractions.
In this table, we have three columns, Tourist
Attractions, Features and Recommendations.
And the three places are the Old Stone
Mine, Workers' Workshop and the Explorer.
In step three, you have to read the
questions, underline keywords, predict paraphrases and what type
of information is missing from each blank.
These are the similar important steps that we
also apply for other question types.
Let's practice these steps for our exercise.
Nice job!
Now you are going to listen and fill
in the correct answers in the practice section.
And as usual, don't forget to check your
answers carefully after you complete all the questions.
See you again soon!
Learn English for free www.engvid.com